[Rhythmic music plays]
[تشغيل الموسيقى الإيقاعية]
[Yuna] I’m going too
[يونا] سأذهب أيضًا
[Sound of car door closing]
[صوت إغلاق باب السيارة]
[mobile phone vibrating sound]
[صوت اهتزاز الهاتف المحمول]
Uh, I'm the assistant manager. You arrived at the parking lot?
آه، أنا مساعد المدير. هل وصلت إلى موقف السيارات؟
I’ll go first too.
سأبدأ أولاً أيضًا.
[Jay] Oh, go
[جاي] أوه، اذهب
[Sigh]
[تنهد]
[Sound of car door opening and closing]
[صوت فتح وإغلاق باب السيارة]
[Meaningful music]
[موسيقى ذات معنى]
[shaking breathing]
[اهتزاز التنفس]
[Scheme] Oh, why did you come here? Are you bothering people?
[مخطط] أوه، لماذا أتيت إلى هنا؟ هل تزعج الناس؟
[dark music]
[الموسيقى المظلمة]
Ah, Yu-jeong came?
آه، جاء يو جيونغ؟
[laughter]
[ضحك]
But I
لكن أنا
Yoojung is with a gangster like you I'm not opposed to getting married
Yoojung مع رجل عصابة مثلك أنا لست ضد الزواج
Are you looking at people anyway?
هل تنظر إلى الناس على أي حال؟
I'm looking at the house.
أنا أنظر إلى المنزل.
[laughter]
[ضحك]
I like your mind
أنا أحب عقلك
Ah, if only Yujeong were as cool as you. I would have been more comfortable
آه، لو أن Yujeong كان رائعًا مثلك. كنت سأكون أكثر راحة
[laughter]
[ضحك]
[nervous music]
[موسيقى عصبية]
So
هكذا
Give it to me
أعطها لي
Is this really it?
هل هذا حقا؟
[Haemi’s strong breathing]
[تنفس هيمي القوي]
[Haemi’s heavy breathing]
[تنفس هيمي الثقيل]
[Yelling harshly]
[الصراخ بقسوة]
- [Doshik’s mean laugh] - [Haemi’s heavy breathing]
- [ضحكة دوشيك اللئيمة] - [تنفس هيمي الثقيل]
-You druggy bitch! - [Haemi’s scream of pain]
- أيتها العاهرة المدمنة للمخدرات! - [صرخة هيمي من الألم]
[Haemi’s heavy breathing]
[تنفس هيمي الثقيل]
[Rough breathing]
[التنفس الخشن]
[Schematic] That’s right, that’s right
[تخطيطي] هذا صحيح، هذا صحيح
Your mom also gives tips from customers
تقدم والدتك أيضًا نصائح من العملاء
I heard you got on your knees and received it?
سمعت أنك جثت على ركبتيك واستلمتها؟
[Doshik’s heavy breathing]
[تنفس دوشيك الثقيل]
[Sharp sound effect]
[تأثير صوت حاد]
[shaking breathing]
[اهتزاز التنفس]
[uneasy music]
[موسيقى مضطربة]
[Haemi’s heavy breathing]
[تنفس هيمي الثقيل]
[Urgent music]
[موسيقى عاجلة]
[Haemi's urgent breathing]
[تنفس هيمي العاجل]
[Haemi’s heavy breathing]
[تنفس هيمي الثقيل]
[Hae-mi’s frightened groan]
[تأوه هاي مي الخائف]
[cell phone vibrates]
[يهتز الهاتف الخليوي]
[President Jeong] To room 707 I sent a delivery man.
[الرئيس جيونج] إلى الغرفة 707 لقد أرسلت رجل التسليم.
Customer's secrets President Jeong will take it to his grave.
أسرار العميل سيأخذها الرئيس جيونج إلى قبره.
[Sound of cell phone closing]
[صوت إغلاق الهاتف الخليوي]
Just once
مرة واحدة فقط
- [Rattling sound] - [Nervous music]
- [صوت قعقعة] - [موسيقى عصبية]
[After exhaling]
[بعد الزفير]
[Sound of car door opening]
[صوت فتح باب السيارة]
[Sound of car door closing]
[صوت إغلاق باب السيارة]
[light sigh]
[تنهد خفيف]
[Button sound]
[صوت الزر]
[Elevator arrival sound]
[صوت وصول المصعد]
[Guidance voice] The door opens
[صوت إرشادي] الباب يُفتح
[Heavy sound effect]
[مؤثرات صوتية ثقيلة]
[Yuna] Did you finish talking with Jay?
[يونا] هل انتهيت من الحديث مع جاي؟
So do you want to talk to me now?
إذن هل تريد التحدث معي الآن؟
[Button sound]
[صوت الزر]
What are you talking about when you stab me in the back?
ما الذي تتحدث عنه عندما تطعنني في ظهري؟
Let me ask you just one thing
اسمحوا لي أن أطلب منك شيئا واحدا فقط
Why did you kill the prayer ceremony?
لماذا قتلت مراسم الصلاة؟
[Yuna] No
[يونا] لا
Kill the prayer ceremony
قتل مراسم الصلاة
Why did you blame me?
لماذا ألومتني؟
Do you trust Dojae more than me?
هل تثق بـ Dojae أكثر مني؟
But don’t trust Dojae too much.
لكن لا تثق بـ Dojae كثيرًا.
Now it's Dojae
الآن حان دوجاي
I hold your hand because of the mask
أمسك يدك بسبب القناع
You never know when he might stab you in the back
أنت لا تعرف أبدًا متى قد يطعنك في الظهر
Still, I'm better than you
ومع ذلك، أنا أفضل منك
Dojae at least
دوجاي على الأقل
Blame it on me You're not running away, are you?
إلقاء اللوم علي أنت لا تهرب، أليس كذلك؟
[Yuna] I’m warning you
[يونا] أنا أحذرك
I held Dojae’s hand If you treat me carelessly
أمسكت بيد دوجاي إذا كنت تعاملني بلا مبالاة
i will kill you
سأقتلك
'Cause I've got nothing to lose
لأنه ليس لدي ما أخسره
- [Button sound] - [Elevator operating sound]
- [صوت الزر] - [صوت تشغيل المصعد]
[Yoojeong] You saw Jae-yi?
[Yoojeong] هل رأيت جاي يي؟
where?
أين؟
In front of Yuna Hotel
امام فندق يونا
It's obvious
هذا واضح
I must have gone to see Yuna.
لا بد أنني ذهبت لرؤية يونا.
[Yoojeong] Why did you go there?
[يوجيونغ] لماذا ذهبت إلى هناك؟
[nervous music]
[موسيقى عصبية]
[Haemi is embarrassed] Today At the Grand Gangbo Hotel
[هيمي محرج] اليوم في فندق جراند جانجبو
There was a seminar
كانت هناك ندوة
Like this?
مثل هذا؟
Is that important to you now?
هل هذا مهم بالنسبة لك الآن؟
Jay is us Maybe he betrayed you?
جاي هو نحن ربما خانك؟
[Yujeong’s sigh] Jae-i
[تنهيدة يوجيونغ] جاي-ي
- Because of the land issue - [Sound of a glass being set down]
- بسبب قضية الأرض - [صوت وضع الزجاج]
Maybe he went?
ربما ذهب؟
Then for over a week
ثم لأكثر من أسبوع
Take a dive with us There's no reason to keep in touch
قم بالغوص معنا ليس هناك سبب للبقاء على اتصال
[sigh]
[تنهد]
If it's as you guess If Jay betrayed us
إذا كان الأمر كما تظن إذا خاننا جاي
What should I do then?
ماذا يجب أن أفعل بعد ذلك؟
I'll give you a weapon
سأعطيك سلاحا
Dojae pierces the solar plexus.
Dojae يخترق الضفيرة الشمسية.
[Chilling sound effect]
[مؤثرات صوتية تقشعر لها الأبدان]
[Yuna] Now
[يونا] الآن
It's yours now
انها لك الآن
thank you
شكرا لك
[Jay] Not that guy
[جاي] ليس هذا الرجل
For giving it to me
لإعطائها لي
I want you to find my daughter Keep your promise
أريدك أن تجد ابنتي حافظ على وعدك
That's all I want
هذا كل ما أريد
[sigh]
[تنهد]
But
لكن
What kind of guy is that? How did you meet?
أي نوع من الرجل هو ذلك؟ كيف التقيتما؟
- [Interesting Music] - [laughter]
- [موسيقى مثيرة للاهتمام] - [ضحك]
Food came out
خرج الطعام
[Yuna] In America
[يونا] في أمريكا
by chance
بالصدفة
To look at me like that Could you please give me more tips?
أن تنظر إلي هكذا هل يمكن أن تعطيني المزيد من النصائح؟
Oh, sorry.
أوه، آسف.
- [Sound of dishes being set down] - Because it looks familiar
- [صوت الأطباق التي يتم وضعها] - لأنه يبدو مألوفا
Maybe
ربما
- Do you know Korea’s Ace Bar? - [Sound of dishes being set down]
- هل تعرف آيس بار الكوري؟ - [صوت الأطباق التي يتم وضعها]
[Jake] I worked there. My name is Jake
[جيك] عملت هناك. اسمي جيك
[Yuna] Now that I know He was a successful host bar player.
[يونا] الآن بعد أن عرفت لقد كان لاعبًا ناجحًا في الحانة.
Host and bar madam
سيدتي المضيفة والبار
each other in a strange land I thought it would be dependable
بعضهم البعض في أرض غريبة اعتقدت أنه سيكون يمكن الاعتماد عليها
[laughter]
[ضحك]
[light laughter]
[ضحكة خفيفة]
But why did you break up?
ولكن لماذا انفصلت؟
Coming to America
القادمة إلى أمريكا
They said it was for reform and reform.
قالوا إنه من أجل الإصلاح والإصلاح.
[Yuna] I believed it
[يونا] لقد صدقت ذلك
Because I'm sick of that floor
لأنني سئمت من هذا الطابق
But
لكن
[Sound of conversation in English]
[صوت المحادثة باللغة الإنجليزية]
[Police clears his throat]
[الشرطة تطهر حلقه]
[Police in English]
[الشرطة باللغة الإنجليزية]
[Police]
[الشرطة]
[Yuna]
[يونا]
[surprised gasp]
[لهث متفاجئ]
- [Yuna’s embarrassed voice] - [Police speaking English]
- [صوت يونا المحرج] - [الشرطة تتحدث الإنجليزية]
[Korean] Without me knowing To VIPs from Korea
[الكورية] دون أن أعرف لكبار الشخصيات من كوريا
Arranging drugs and prostitution
ترتيب المخدرات والدعارة
[laughter]
[ضحك]
They even gave you a replacement?
حتى أنهم أعطوك بديلاً؟
in that dirty work using my account
في ذلك العمل القذر باستخدام حسابي
I turned everything over
لقد قلبت كل شيء
[Yuna] ‘Where did you go?’
[يونا] "أين ذهبت؟"
[Yuna] While we’re resolving that
[يونا] بينما نعمل على حل ذلك
I ran away with Nana.
لقد هربت مع نانا.
'My Baby'
"طفلي"
The bastard
اللقيط
But
لكن
[Jay] You did that to me The guy who ran away
[جاي] لقد فعلت ذلك بي الرجل الذي هرب
I met you in America
التقيت بك في أمريكا
Is it a coincidence?
هل هي صدفة؟
[dark music]
[الموسيقى المظلمة]
When I lived with that guy
عندما كنت أعيش مع ذلك الرجل
A photo I took with you guys I've shown it to you before
صورة التقطتها معكم يا رفاق لقد أظهرت لك من قبل
[Yuna] Among those four friends, you and me
[يونا] من بين هؤلاء الأصدقاء الأربعة، أنت وأنا
Now even Yujeong is involved.
الآن حتى Yujeong متورط.
How could that be a coincidence?
كيف يمكن أن يكون ذلك صدفة؟
Then all of this
ثم كل هذا
A painting by Ki Yun-cheol?
لوحة لكي يون تشيول؟
No, for what?
لا، لماذا؟
well
حسنا
I don’t know what it is [sigh]
لا أعرف ما هو [تنهد]
I guess it's true that they are terribly intertwined.
أعتقد أنه صحيح أنهم متشابكون بشكل رهيب.
[Yuna] By the way
[يونا] بالمناسبة
To Yujeong
إلى يوجيونج
That guy is the guy who raped you. Are you going to tell me?
هذا الرجل هو الرجل الذي اغتصبك. هل ستخبرني؟
[Jehyuk] But if possible, That you and I did it together
[جيهيوك] ولكن إذا أمكن، أن أنت وأنا فعلنا ذلك معًا
Please keep it a secret from Yujeong.
من فضلك أبقِ الأمر سراً عن Yujeong.
With that neat personality
بتلك الشخصية الأنيقة
How much it hurts
كم يؤلم
well
حسنا
Yoojeong
يوجيونغ
Will you believe me?
هل تصدقني؟
I think you might misunderstand it differently.
أعتقد أنك قد تسيء فهم الأمر بشكل مختلف.
Then what I'm saying to Yujeong is Hold on for a moment
إذن ما أقوله لـ Yujeong هو انتظر للحظة
[Yuna] I want my daughter’s safety need to worry
[يونا] أريد سلامة ابنتي بحاجة للقلق
If Yoojeong
إذا يوجيونغ
Even if I find out that Nana is my daughter
حتى لو اكتشفت أن نانا هي ابنتي
[Yuna] Like now I don't know if I'll be pretty
[يونا] مثل الآن لا أعرف إذا كنت سأكون جميلة
Then
ثم
[Jay] I am Song Je-hyuk If you take off that damn mask
[جاي] أنا سونغ جي هيوك إذا خلعت هذا القناع اللعين
Even Yujeong will trust me then.
حتى Yujeong سوف يثق بي حينها.
[Yuna] How are you going to take it off?
[يونا] كيف ستخلعينه؟
As he said
كما قال
This mask is you It's not proof of sexual assault.
هذا القناع هو أنت إنه ليس دليلاً على الاعتداء الجنسي.
I'll make you a star
سأجعلك نجمة
star? Song Je-hyuk?
نجمة؟ سونغ جي هيوك؟
That guy is in the shadows If he was active like that
هذا الرجل في الظل إذا كان نشطا من هذا القبيل
It's hard to show to the outside world
من الصعب أن تظهر للعالم الخارجي
[Jay] Pull it up to the surface If you make it a star
[جاي] اسحبه إلى السطح إذا جعلته نجما
No matter how perfect the mask is,
مهما كان القناع مثاليا،
The bare face is revealed
تم الكشف عن الوجه العاري
[surprised gasp]
[شهقة متفاجئة]
[secret music]
[الموسيقى السرية]
Then you take charge of the brisket.
ثم تتولى مسؤولية بريسكيت.
[Yuna] I’ll take charge of the dark side
[يونا] سأتولى مسؤولية الجانب المظلم
It will be easier if you press up and down.
سيكون الأمر أسهل إذا قمت بالضغط لأعلى ولأسفل.
Can you do it?
هل يمكنك فعل ذلك؟
Anyway, he's your ex-husband.
على أية حال، فهو زوجك السابق.
I'm more worried about you
أنا أكثر قلقا عليك
Anyway, Yoo-jeong is her husband.
على أية حال، يو جيونغ هو زوجها.
Let’s do our best, Go Yoo-na.
دعونا نبذل قصارى جهدنا، جو يو نا.
[Jehyuk] Sometimes Nana looks for you
[جيهيوك] أحيانًا تبحث نانا عنك
remember
تذكر
me, you, my daughter
أنا، أنت، ابنتي
We had a good time in America
لقد قضينا وقتًا ممتعًا في أمريكا
[Yuna] Then
[يونا] إذن
Can you show me?
هل يمكنك أن تريني؟
Do your best, Dojae.
بذل قصارى جهدك، دوجاي.
[Secretary Choi] You couldn’t find the mask?
[السكرتير تشوي] ألم تتمكن من العثور على القناع؟
[Jehyuk] Yoo Yoo and that
[جيهيوك] يو يو وذاك
I handed it over to Dojae.
لقد سلمتها إلى Dojae.
Hey
مهلا
[Sound of Secretary Choi taking a deep breath]
[صوت الوزير تشوي وهو يأخذ نفسا عميقا]
No, then Song Je-hyuk Doesn’t it become more dangerous?
لا، ثم سونغ جي هيوك ألا يصبح الأمر أكثر خطورة؟
[Secretary Choi] That mask is
[الوزير تشوي] هذا القناع
With Dojae rather than Go Yoo Na Because it's more relevant.
مع Dojae بدلاً من Go Yoo Na لأنه أكثر أهمية.
So tell this to Representative Ki.
لذا أخبر هذا للممثل كي.
No matter what I do
بغض النظر عما أفعله
Do Jae-i becomes the mayor of Tongju Stop it
أصبح "دو جاي-ي" عمدة مدينة "تونجو". أوقفه
[Jehyuk] Otherwise, it’s not just me
[جيهيوك] بخلاف ذلك، لست أنا فقط
The whole Angels Club You might get stepped on
نادي الملائكة كله قد يتم الدوس عليك
[nervous music]
[موسيقى عصبية]
[Kanghu’s sigh]
[تنهد كانغو]
[Jay] The evidence I have and
[جاي] الأدلة لدي و
The blood DNA on the mask It matches
الحمض النووي للدم الموجود على القناع يتطابق
[Sound of paper turning]
[صوت تقليب الورق]
Now that guy is the culprit
الآن هذا الرجل هو الجاني
It became clear
أصبح واضحا
But how did you do that? You can clean your identity, right?
ولكن كيف فعلت ذلك؟ يمكنك تنظيف هويتك، أليس كذلك؟
[Yongpil] In the name of Song Jehyuk
[يونغبيل] باسم سونغ جيهيوك
violation of traffic laws Didn't take off a single ticket
انتهاك قوانين المرور لم أقلع تذكرة واحدة
[Jay’s sigh] Mayor Jeong Gu-tae Please contact the chairman of the sponsoring association.
[تنهد جاي] العمدة جيونج جو تاي يرجى الاتصال برئيس الجمعية الراعية.
From now on, in the Tongju mayoral election sold out
من الآن فصاعدا، في انتخابات رئاسة بلدية تونغجو بيعت
[Calm music]
[موسيقى هادئة]
[Heavy sound effect]
[مؤثرات صوتية ثقيلة]
[Kanghu] Yuna, I’m Kanghu
[كانغو] يونا، أنا كانغو
Can I meet you for a moment?
هل يمكنني مقابلتك للحظة؟
[Sound of cell phone closing]
[صوت إغلاق الهاتف الخليوي]
[Jay] Mayor Jeong Gu-tae when you were alive
[جاي] العمدة جيونج جو تاي عندما كنت على قيد الحياة
I used to come here often
اعتدت أن آتي إلى هنا في كثير من الأحيان
True every time I remember eating it deliciously.
صحيح في كل مرة أتذكر أكله لذيذ.
this restaurant
هذا المطعم
The chairman of the sponsoring association You run it, right?
رئيس الجمعية الراعية أنت تقوم بتشغيله، أليس كذلك؟
Oh, yeah, well, well, yeah
أوه، نعم، حسنًا، حسنًا، نعم
At the minister's celebration party
في حفل احتفال الوزير
[Jay] Mayor Jeong Gu-tae
[جاي] العمدة جيونج جو تاي
You said that.
قلت ذلك.
As mayor's successor
كخليفة للعمدة
You think of me
أنت تفكر بي
Chairman
رئيس
In this mayoral election
في هذه الانتخابات البلدية
My sponsoring chairman How about becoming one?
الرئيس الراعية لي ماذا عن أن تصبح واحدًا؟
Uh, that…
اه، أن...
[Sound of intake of breath]
[صوت أخذ نفس]
That's so...
هذا هكذا...
[Sponsoring Chairman] Oh my
[الرئيس الراعي] يا إلهي
Are you here?
هل أنت هنا؟
[dark music]
[الموسيقى المظلمة]
- [Yuncheol] Sit down, sit down - [Sponsoring Chairman] Ah, yes
- [يونتشول] اجلس، اجلس - [الرئيس الراعي] آه، نعم
[Kichul’s light smile]
[ابتسامة كيشول الخفيفة]
This is someone who should know.
هذا هو الشخص الذي يجب أن يعرف.
At someone else's meal
في وجبة شخص آخر
You can't intervene.
لا يمكنك التدخل.
[Laughs] Well, actually
[يضحك] حسنًا، في الواقع
[Yuncheol] Here to the chairman I came here because I had some business to do.
[يونتشيول] هنا للرئيس لقد جئت إلى هنا لأن لدي بعض الأعمال لأقوم بها.
Because the recommendation to cancel the correction order was processed
لأنه تمت معالجة التوصية بإلغاء أمر التصحيح
You can relax now
يمكنك الاسترخاء الآن
[Sponsoring Chairman] Oh my
[الرئيس الراعي] يا إلهي
Thank you, Senator, thank you.
شكرا لك، السيناتور، شكرا لك.
- [light laughter] - [Sponsoring Chairman’s happy laughter]
- [ضحكة خفيفة] - [رعاية الضحكة السعيدة لرئيس مجلس الإدارة]
Ah, here’s the chairman.
آه، هنا الرئيس.
Blink by mistake
وميض عن طريق الخطأ
This store You did an illegal expansion?
هذا المتجر هل قمت بالتوسع غير القانوني؟
[Yuncheol] This restaurant I have been a regular customer for decades
[يونتشيول] هذا المطعم لقد كنت عميلاً منتظمًا منذ عقود
can you stay still
هل يمكنك البقاء ساكنا؟
I helped you a bit.
لقد ساعدتك قليلا.
Oh, hey, Chairman.
أوه، مهلا، الرئيس.
Could you please give me some acorn jelly?
هل يمكن أن تعطيني بعض هلام البلوط من فضلك؟
It's not on the menu
إنه ليس في القائمة
How delicious it was
كم كان لذيذا
- [Yuncheol’s laughter] - [Sponsoring Chairman] Ah, yes
- [ضحك يونتشيول] - [الرئيس الراعي] آه، نعم
[Sponsoring Chairman] Soon I'll make it for you, yeah [laughter]
[الرئيس الراعي] قريبا سأصنعه لك، نعم [ضحك]
Only in Tongju
فقط في تونغجو
25 years as a member of the National Assembly
25 عاماً عضواً في مجلس الأمة
Something that has no basis whatsoever, what?
شيء ليس له أي أساس على الإطلاق، ماذا؟
[Yun Cheol] You want to become mayor?
[يون تشيول] هل تريد أن تصبح عمدة؟
- [Snort] - [Sound of clattering chopsticks]
- [شخير] - [صوت قعقعة عيدان تناول الطعام]
If you try to eat it raw like this
إذا حاولت أن تأكله نيئًا بهذه الطريقة
I'm sick, I'm sick
أنا مريض، أنا مريض
By now
الآن
Misconceptions about me I think you solved it?
اعتقادات خاطئة عني أعتقد أنك حللت ذلك؟
The real culprit who killed my son
الجاني الحقيقي الذي قتل ابني
Does anyone really have any doubts?
هل لدى أي شخص حقا أي شكوك؟
[Jay] Take a good look
[جاي] ألق نظرة جيدة
The saying ‘it is dark under the lamp’ As you think about it
المثل "الظلام تحت المصباح" كما تفكر في ذلك
[Call connection tone]
[نغمة اتصال المكالمة]
Uh, senior?
اه كبار؟
[Atmospheric music plays]
[تشغيل الموسيقى الجوية]
[Sound of Hae-mi catching her breath] Isn’t it strange?
[صوت هاي مي تلتقط أنفاسها] أليس هذا غريبا؟
This pasta has all kinds of ingredients.
تحتوي هذه المعكرونة على جميع أنواع المكونات.
- It's all in there. - [Sound of picking with a fork]
- كل شيء هناك. - [صوت الالتقاط بالشوكة]
last posted A few pieces of this black truffle
آخر نشر بضع قطع من هذه الكمأة السوداء
This pasta scent They take over everything.
رائحة المعكرونة هذه إنهم يستولون على كل شيء.
[sigh]
[تنهد]
you are really good at speed
أنت جيد حقًا في السرعة
When I see the rice being passed over
عندما أرى الأرز يتم تمريره
[laughter]
[ضحك]
- [Sigh] - [Sound of fork being put down]
- [تنهد] - [صوت وضع الشوكة]
What is this?
ما هذا؟
My black truffle?
الكمأة السوداء الخاصة بي؟
what?
ماذا؟
Jay that's it
جاي هذا كل شيء
Jeong Gu-tae's family After processing, the fee received
عائلة جيونج جو تاي بعد المعالجة، تم استلام الرسوم
through my mom's store I washed it
من خلال متجر أمي لقد غسلته
[heavy music]
[موسيقى ثقيلة]
[Haemi] I have this
[هيمي] لدي هذا
We will occupy the land of Tongzhou City.
سوف نحتل أرض مدينة تونغتشو.
[Savoring elasticity]
[المرونة المذاق]
[Sound of paper turning]
[صوت تقليب الورق]
With this, Jay Are you trying to threaten me?
مع هذا، جاي هل تحاول تهديدي؟
[Laughing] What is a threat?
[يضحك] ما هو التهديد؟
It's called black truffle.
يطلق عليه الكمأة السوداء.
- [Haemi] Let’s just watch the situation first. - [Sound of fork being put down]
- [هايمي] دعونا نشاهد الوضع أولاً. - [هذا هو الحال بالنسبة لي]
Either hand it over to Jay or not. Hand it over to Ki Yun-cheol.
إما تسليمها إلى جاي أم لا. Hand it over to Ki Yun-cheol.
I just need to secure the land
أنا فقط بحاجة لتأمين الأرض
This
هذا
[Yoojeong] Is there anything in the file?
[Yoojeong] هل هناك أي شيء في الملف؟
[Laughing] My mom You're old.
[تضحك] أمي أنت قديم.
That ledger is unique
هذا دفتر الأستاذ فريد من نوعه
[Sound of Hae-mi taking a deep breath]
[صوت هاي مي وهي تأخذ نفسًا عميقًا]
[Haemi] Maybe you too If you want to share it
[هيمي] ربما أنت أيضًا إذا كنت ترغب في مشاركتها
taken from our hotel
مأخوذة من فندقنا
- Give me 10 billion first! - [Yujeong’s surprised gasp]
- أعطني 10 مليار أولا! - [شهقة يوجيونغ المفاجئة]
[Sound of clicking tongue]
[صوت نقر اللسان]
- Oh, really. - [Sound of a ledger being closed]
- أوه، حقا. - [صوت إغلاق دفتر الأستاذ]
Okay, I'll give it back, okay?
حسنًا، سأعيدها، حسنًا؟
[light laughter]
[ضحكة خفيفة]
[Haemi] How about newlywed fun?
[هيمي] ماذا عن متعة المتزوجين حديثًا؟
good?
جيد؟
[Jehyuk] Why do you keep Are you being dragged around by your friends?
[جيهيوك] لماذا تبقي هل يتم جرك من قبل أصدقائك؟
Are you Mojiri?
هل أنت موجيري؟
just
فقط
Is it different from before marriage?
وهل يختلف عما كان عليه قبل الزواج؟
It seems like things have changed a bit
يبدو أن الأمور قد تغيرت قليلا
[bursts of laughter]
[ رشقات من الضحك ]
Hey, I'm getting married Are there some men who don’t change?
ها أنا سأتزوج هل هناك بعض الرجال الذين لا يتغيرون؟
Ah, all men change, all
آه، كل الرجال يتغيرون، كلهم
[Haemi’s laughter]
[ضحك هيمي]
Right?
أليس كذلك؟
That's it, right?
هذا كل شيء، أليس كذلك؟
[Sound of clicking tongue]
[صوت نقر اللسان]
I'm more worried about Nana than Jehyuk.
أنا قلقة على نانا أكثر من جيهيوك.
Sometimes I meet you and you make me happy It’s different from raising them at all.
أحيانًا أقابلك وتسعدني إنه يختلف عن تربيتهم على الإطلاق.
[Sound of dishes being set down]
[صوت الأطباق التي يتم وضعها]
Yes
نعم
[Yoojeong] Since we met Nana
[Yoojeong] منذ أن التقينا نانا
It's only been a year
لقد مرت سنة واحدة فقط
As if from the beginning like you were my baby
كما لو كان من البداية كما لو كنت طفلي
It's so so pretty I'm going crazy
إنها جميلة جدًا لدرجة أنني سأصاب بالجنون
Now the world without me
الآن العالم بدوني
It's so unimaginable?
إنه أمر لا يمكن تصوره إلى هذا الحد؟
Then it's a bigger problem?
ثم انها مشكلة أكبر؟
[Haemi] When my real mother comes to visit What are you going to do?
[هيمي] عندما تأتي والدتي الحقيقية للزيارة ماذا ستفعل؟
This is a woman who committed a crime and went to prison.
هذه امرأة ارتكبت جريمة ودخلت السجن.
What right do you have to come to Nana?
بأي حق عليك أن تأتي إلى نانا؟
What does prison have to do with your real mother? If you gave birth, you are the biological mother.
ما علاقة السجن بأمك الحقيقية؟ إذا أنجبت، فأنت الأم البيولوجية.
[Haemi’s worried breathing]
[تنفس هيمي القلق]
I rather use the excuse that that woman is me.
أفضّل استخدام العذر بأن تلك المرأة هي أنا.
- I'm worried that it will shake up Jehyuk too. - [Heavy music]
- أنا قلق من أن ذلك سيهز جيهيوك أيضًا. - [موسيقى ثقيلة]
[light sigh]
[تنهد خفيف]
Ah, so why are you like that? Are you married to a complicated man?
آه، فلماذا أنت هكذا؟ هل أنت متزوجة من رجل معقد؟
[Haemi clicks her tongue]
[هيمي تنقر على لسانها]
[Haemi] Like me I should have done it with a simple man.
[هايمي] مثلي كان يجب أن أفعل ذلك مع رجل بسيط.
[Savoring breathing]
[تذوق التنفس]
[President Jeong] Mariela Hotel In the suite
[الرئيس جيونج] فندق مارييلا في الجناح
Is there a VVIP member waiting for you?
هل هناك عضو VVIP في انتظارك؟
I bring you a gift
أحضر لك هدية
I put the things you need in it.
أضع الأشياء التي تحتاجها فيه.
I'll tell you
سأخبرك
It's for my sister, my sister
إنها لأختي، أختي
[Leo] I only There is only one sister, Haemi.
[ليو] أنا فقط هناك أخت واحدة فقط، هيمي.
Okay, it's okay.
حسنًا، لا بأس.
[Nervous breathing]
[التنفس العصبي]
VIP-only elevator Where is it?
مصعد لكبار الشخصيات فقط أين هو؟
- [Employee] You can go here. - thank you
- [الموظف] يمكنك الذهاب هنا. - شكرا لك
[Employee] Yes, thank you
[الموظف] نعم، شكرًا لك
[Employee] Hello.
[الموظف] مرحبا.
That person just now What were you asking?
هذا الشخص للتو ماذا كنت تسأل؟
[Employee] Ah, to the VIP-only elevator. You asked for the direction
[الموظف] آه، إلى المصعد المخصص لكبار الشخصيات فقط. لقد طلبت الاتجاه
Ah, yes
اه نعم
[Doorbell sounds]
[أصوات جرس الباب]
[Sound of door opening]
[صوت فتح الباب]
[Light elasticity]
[مرونة خفيفة]
- Hey, this flower delivery. - [Woman’s surprised gasp]
- مهلا، تسليم هذه الزهور. - [여자의 놀란 숨소리]
I think I came to the wrong place?
أعتقد أنني أتيت إلى المكان الخطأ؟
[Leo] Here is a gift
[ليو] هنا هدية
- [Sound of door opening and closing] - Is it really okay if I don’t take you there?
- [صوت فتح وإغلاق الباب] - هل هو بخير حقًا إذا لم آخذك إلى هناك؟
The hotel is just around the corner.
الفندق قاب قوسين أو أدنى.
- Then I'm leaving. - [Yoojeong] Yes
- ثم سأغادر. - [يوجيونغ] نعم
[Branch Manager] No more
[مدير الفرع] لا أكثر
How much money do you have to repay now? Another loan?
كم من المال لديك لسداد الآن؟ قرض آخر؟
[Yoojeong] Received from Mariela Hotel That's because I have to pay back the donation.
[يوجيونغ] تم استلامه من فندق مارييلا ذلك لأنني يجب أن أدفع التبرع.
Even if we use our office building as collateral. How could it not?
حتى لو استخدمنا مبنى مكاتبنا كضمان. كيف لا؟
I'm talking about that donation.
أنا أتحدث عن هذا التبرع.
- [Branch Manager] Financial District Jjirasie - [Dark Music]
- [مدير الفرع] المنطقة المالية في جيراسي - [موسيقى داكنة]
Rumors are going around
الشائعات تدور
Because of the land lawsuit
بسبب دعوى الأرض
I can't move
لا أستطيع التحرك
The culture and arts complex
مجمع الثقافة والفنون
Is it true that the Youngun Foundation does this?
هل صحيح أن مؤسسة يونغون تفعل ذلك؟
[sigh]
[تنهد]
[Cell phone operation sound]
[صوت تشغيل الهاتف الخليوي]
[Call connection tone]
[نغمة اتصال المكالمة]
Ah, aunt
آه، عمة
Yes, I'm on my way home.
نعم، أنا في طريقي إلى المنزل.
Did you pick up Nana?
هل التقطت نانا؟
[Woman] Oh, no
[المرأة] أوه، لا
Well, I got a call from the chairman. I said I would pick it up myself.
حسنًا، لقد تلقيت مكالمة من الرئيس. قلت أنني سألتقطها بنفسي.
[Surprising gasp] But Did you stop by the playground? You're a little late.
[لهث مفاجئ] لكن هل توقفت عند الملعب؟ لقد تأخرت قليلا.
Are you Jehyuk?
Are you Jehyuk?
yes, i understand
نعم، أنا أفهم
[Cell phone operation sound]
[صوت تشغيل الهاتف الخليوي]
At the playground?
في الملعب؟
Please go to the playground
يرجى الذهاب إلى الملعب
[heavy music]
[موسيقى ثقيلة]
[Children talking]
[أطفال يتحدثون]
[Children's laughter]
[ضحك الأطفال]
Who are you?
من أنت؟
if
لو
Do you remember me?
هل تتذكرني؟
I'm Anna...
انا آنا...
Oh no
أوه لا
I remember me too
أتذكرني أيضًا
I don't know
لا أعرف
[Nana] But lady Why are you crying?
[نانا] لكن سيدة لماذا تبكي؟
[laughter mixed with tears]
[ضحكة ممزوجة بالدموع]
just
فقط
[Crying breath] Nana Because it’s so pretty
[نفس البكاء] نانا لأنها جميلة جدا
The lady is pretty too
السيدة جميلة أيضاً
My mom is prettier though
أمي أجمل بالرغم من ذلك
[sniffling sound]
[صوت الاستنشاق]
Nana
نانا
Can I touch it?
هل يمكنني لمسها؟
[Yuna’s trembling breathing]
[تنفس يونا المرتجف]
[sniffling sound]
[صوت الاستنشاق]
[Soaring music]
[موسيقى صاخبة]
[breathing sound]
[صوت التنفس]
[Yuna’s sobbing]
[يونا تبكي]
[Yuna continues to sob]
[تستمر يونا بالبكاء]
Huh? Wait a minute
هاه؟ انتظر لحظة
[nervous music]
[موسيقى عصبية]
[Sound of car door closing]
[صوت إغلاق باب السيارة]
Because I listened to what you wanted Now it's my turn
لأنني استمعت إلى ما أردت الآن حان دوري
[Jehyuk] Tell me
[جيهيوك] أخبرني
Dojae
دوجاي
What are your future plans?
ما هي خططك المستقبلية؟
Nothing much yet
لا يوجد الكثير حتى الآن
I'll let you know when I see movement
سأخبرك عندما أرى الحركة
If you still want to see Nana You'll have to do it right
إذا كنت لا تزال تريد رؤية نانا سيكون عليك القيام بذلك بشكل صحيح
I have a question
لدي سؤال
[Yuna] Yoojeong caught it You even became the chairman of the foundation.
[يونا] أمسكتها Yoojeong حتى أنك أصبحت رئيسًا للمؤسسة.
- But why are you so greedy? - [Nervous music]
- ولكن لماذا أنت الجشع جدا؟ - [موسيقى عصبية]
Doing secret business
ممارسة الأعمال السرية
It's instinct
إنها غريزة
Just as you cling to your maternal instinct
تمامًا كما تتشبث بغريزة الأمومة لديك
my instinct is money
غريزتي هي المال
I have some strength Things that ignored me
لدي بعض القوة الأشياء التي تجاهلتني
Put it under my feet and dominate it.
ضعه تحت قدمي وسيطر عليه.
That's
هذا
For that to happen, it is a necessary project.
ولكي يحدث ذلك، فهو مشروع ضروري.
If it's a business
إذا كان عملا
That club or something?
هذا النادي أو شيء من هذا؟
[snort]
[شخير]
At least I should know something let me help you
على الأقل يجب أن أعرف شيئا اسمحوا لي أن أساعدك
[Soaring music]
[موسيقى صاخبة]
Still you
لا تزال أنت
You're the kid's dad, right?
أنت والد الطفل، أليس كذلك؟
Don't go to Ace Bar.
لا تذهب إلى Ace Bar.
Because I don’t want you to get hurt either.
لأنني لا أريدك أن تتأذى أيضًا.
[Jehyuk] Still you
[جيهيوك] ما زلت أنت
You're the kid's mom, right?
أنت والدة الطفل، أليس كذلك؟
Yujeong is still with us
Yujeong لا يزال معنا
Don't you know?
ألا تعلم؟
- [Sound of door opening and closing] - [Nana] Mom!
- [صوت فتح وإغلاق الباب] - [نانا] أمي!
[Yoojeong] Uh, is my Nana here?
[يوجيونغ] اه، هل نانا هنا؟
It's me
هذا أنا
Did you have a good time?
هل قضيت وقتا ممتعا؟
[Nana] I drew it in kindergarten today
[نانا] لقد رسمتها في روضة الأطفال اليوم
[Surprise gasp] Really?
[شهقة مفاجئة] حقا؟
Let's see
دعونا نرى
[Yujeong is surprised] Wow, you drew it well.
[تفاجأ يوجيونغ] واو، لقد رسمتها جيدًا.
[Impressed exclamation] Thank you so much It's me
[تعجب معجب] شكرا جزيلا هذا أنا
Mom now
أمي الآن
Without me or me I don't think I can survive even a day
بدوني أو أنا لا أعتقد أنني أستطيع البقاء على قيد الحياة ولو ليوم واحد
I love you, my daughter [laughter]
أحبك يا ابنتي [ضحك]
Oh, but it's me
أوه، ولكن هذا أنا
Where did you go with dad earlier?
أين ذهبت مع أبي في وقت سابق؟
It wasn't there because I went to the playground?
لم يكن هناك لأنني ذهبت إلى الملعب؟
I went to another playground
ذهبت إلى ملعب آخر
But there I played with a certain lady
ولكن هناك لقد لعبت مع سيدة معينة
What kind of lady?
أي نوع من السيدة؟
My dad knows this woman
والدي يعرف هذه المرأة
[Nana] That lady too You look pretty like your mom
[نانا] تلك السيدة أيضًا أنت تبدو جميلة مثل والدتك
[uneasy music]
[موسيقى مضطربة]
[Nervous breathing]
[التنفس العصبي]
[Jungho] The person waiting Who is it?
[Jungho] الشخص المنتظر من هذا؟
[Senior] Ah, Chairman. You will find out when you go in.
[كبار] آه، الرئيس. ستكتشف ذلك عندما تدخل.
To arrogant lawyer Do Jae-i Shall we get a drink?
إلى المحامي المتغطرس دو جاي آي هل سنحصل على مشروب؟
- [Jungho] What are you doing? Now, huh? - [Sound of a kettle being put down]
- [جونغ هو] ماذا تفعل؟ الآن، هاه؟ - [صوت وضع الغلاية جانباً]
I'm trying to upset the situation.
أحاول أن أزعج الوضع.
Hey, are you out of your mind right now?
مهلا، هل أنت خارج عقلك الآن؟
[Senior] I’m sorry
[كبار] أنا آسف
Do-byeon also asked for a favor.
كما طلب دو بيون معروفًا.
[Jungho] It’s done.
[جونغهو] لقد انتهيت.
I have nothing to do with you
ليس لدي أي علاقة معك
Today is not the Do Jae of those days.
اليوم ليس دو جاي في تلك الأيام.
please give me one more chance
من فضلك أعطني فرصة أخرى
[Sound of a kettle being set down]
[صوت غلاية يتم وضعها]
It was really rude back then.
لقد كان وقحا حقا في ذلك الوقت.
Kim Joong-ho, Chairman of Nomination Management
كيم جونغ هو، رئيس إدارة الترشيحات
[Jungho] I ran for the Tongju mayoral election. There will be no need to get nominated anymore.
[Jungho] لقد ترشحت لانتخابات رئاسة بلدية تونغجو. لن تكون هناك حاجة للترشيح بعد الآن.
Write it to me for some reason Has your attitude changed like this?
اكتب لي لسبب ما هل تغير موقفك إلى هذا الحد؟
I am new to politics and
أنا جديد في السياسة و
Because he is an independent candidate
لأنه مرشح مستقل
[Jay] Will you support me on this floor? The elderly are not there
[جاي] هل ستدعمني في هذا الطابق؟ كبار السن ليسوا هناك
Representative Ki Yun-cheol of the Liberty Korea Party and
الممثل كي يون تشيول من حزب كوريا الحرية
the only one able to stand shoulder to shoulder
الوحيد قادرة على الوقوف جنبا إلى جنب
Jeonghandang Chairman Kim Jung-ho
رئيس جيونج هاندانغ كيم جونغ هو
[Jay] My political supporter If you can be
[جاي] مؤيدي السياسي إذا كنت تستطيع أن تكون
more than this I don't think it can be an honor
أكثر من هذا لا أعتقد أنه يمكن أن يكون شرفا
Give me a drink
أعطني شرابا
- They're asking for everything. - [Senior’s light smile]
- إنهم يطلبون كل شيء. - [ابتسامة كبار السن الخفيفة]
[Joongho’s heavy breathing]
[تنفس جونغهو الثقيل]
[Jungho] With rude language
[Jungho] بلغة فظة
I am Lawyer Jae-i Do. If you become a political supporter
أنا المحامي جاي دو. إذا أصبحت مؤيدا سياسيا
What do I get?
ماذا أحصل؟
Chairman If you just do that
رئيس إذا كنت تفعل ذلك فقط
That
ذلك
You will have Dojae.
سيكون لديك دوجاي.
[secret music]
[الموسيقى السرية]
[camera shutter sound]
[صوت مصراع الكاميرا]
[applause]
[تصفيق]
[Sangkuk] Lee Jeonghandang, Liberty Korea Party
[سانغكوك] لي جيونغ هاندانغ، حزب كوريا الحرية
These two major political parties I feel disgusted with old politics
هذين الحزبين السياسيين الرئيسيين أشعر بالاشمئزاز من السياسة القديمة
As a refreshing independent candidate You said you came out
كمرشح مستقل منعش قلت أنك خرجت
Now, like this
الآن، مثل هذا
You joined the Jeonghandang. What was the trigger?
لقد انضممت إلى Jeonghandang. ما هو الزناد؟
[Jay] With all my promises
[جاي] مع كل وعودي
It will become a landmark of Tongzhou City. A cultural and artistic complex was proposed.
وسوف يصبح معلما لمدينة تونغتشو. تم اقتراح مجمع ثقافي وفني.
In order to carry out that promise
ومن أجل تنفيذ ذلك الوعد
I have a strong organization behind me. I realized I needed it
لدي منظمة قوية ورائي. أدركت أنني في حاجة إليها
[Reporter] Candidate Jae-i Do After becoming a candidate for the Jeonghan Party,
[المراسل] المرشح جاي دو بعد أن أصبح مرشحًا لحزب جونغهان،
Naturally, the Liberty Korea Party candidate I'll be your biggest rival
وبطبيعة الحال، مرشح حزب كوريا الحرية سأكون أكبر منافس لك
Among the candidates currently being discussed
ومن بين المرشحين الذين تتم مناقشتهم حاليا
which candidate Are you keeping an eye on it?
أي مرشح هل تراقب ذلك؟
surpassing me Unless a fresh candidate emerges
متفوق علي إلا إذا ظهر مرشح جديد
[Jay on TV] Something that could be powerful There are no candidates?
[جاي على التلفاز] شيء يمكن أن يكون قويًا لا يوجد مرشحين؟
[Camera shutter sound on TV]
[صوت مصراع الكاميرا على شاشة التلفزيون]
[Sim-ok] Our Jay
[سيم أوك] جاي الخاص بنا
mayor approval rating You know we’re running in first place, right?
تصنيف موافقة العمدة أنت تعلم أننا نتنافس في المركز الأول، أليس كذلك؟
People in the market here are already
الناس في السوق هنا بالفعل
My granddaughter became mayor It's just a mess, it's a mess [laughter]
حفيدتي أصبحت عمدة إنها مجرد فوضى، إنها فوضى [ضحك]
[Ilgu] As usual The table setting has changed a bit.
[إلغو] كالعادة لقد تغير إعداد الجدول قليلاً.
[Sim-ok] Oh my, it has to be different.
[سيم-أوك] يا إلهي، يجب أن يكون الأمر مختلفًا.
I'm going to charge more for food than usual.
سأتقاضى ثمن الطعام أكثر من المعتاد.
- How much do you need? - [Meaningful music]
- كم تحتاج؟ - [موسيقى ذات معنى]
[Sim-ok] Um, our Jay Enough to hold an election?
[سيم-أوك] أم، جاي لدينا هل يكفي لإجراء الانتخابات؟
I will deposit money
سوف أقوم بإيداع الأموال
Money alone isn't enough My daughter is running for election.
المال وحده لا يكفي ابنتي تترشح للانتخابات.
The obstacle in front of Jae-yi Clean it up like this
العائق أمام جاي يي تنظيفه مثل هذا
Oh, you can do it.
أوه، يمكنك أن تفعل ذلك.
I'll try
سأحاول
[Employee] We haven’t opened yet.
[الموظف] لم نفتتح بعد.
Uh, hello
اه مرحبا
Boss Jeong, are you ready to go to work yet?
أيها الزعيم جيونج، هل أنت مستعد للذهاب إلى العمل بعد؟
Today
اليوم
Are you here to see Mingi?
هل أنت هنا لرؤية مينجي؟
[Yuna] Drink
[يونا] اشرب
[Mingi] Ah, my job is Because I'm not a player
[مينجي] آه، وظيفتي هي لأنني لست لاعبا
Would you like me to call someone?
هل تريد مني أن أتصل بشخص ما؟
I came to see you
جئت لرؤيتك
I'm better than the players
أنا أفضل من اللاعبين
Are you more attracted to me?
هل أنت منجذب لي أكثر؟
The mask is novel
القناع رواية
[dark music]
[الموسيقى المظلمة]
What do you think?
ما رأيك؟
[Yuna] Playing as a real player is
[يونا] اللعب كلاعب حقيقي
Rather than delivering alcohol to my sisters
بدلاً من توصيل الكحول لأخواتي
With my sisters Don't you like drinking alcohol?
مع أخواتي ألا تحب شرب الكحول؟
President Jeong I'm not that one...
الرئيس جيونج أنا لست ذلك الشخص...
What does he know?
ماذا يعرف؟
A man sees a woman accurately
الرجل يرى المرأة بدقة
[Yuna] You know Leo, right?
[يونا] أنت تعرف ليو، أليس كذلك؟
his wife
زوجته
Did I tie it up?
هل قمت بربطه؟
What can I do?
ماذا يمكنني أن أفعل؟
[People's exclamation]
[تعجب الناس]
[People laughing and applauding]
[الناس يضحكون ويصفقون]
[Jay] Please take care of me
[جاي] من فضلك اعتني بي
[Man 1] Oh, that’s good.
[رجل 1] أوه، هذا جيد.
- You're a total drinker, a drinker. - [Jay’s light laughter]
- أنت شارب كلي، شارب. - [ضحكة جاي الخفيفة]
[Man 2] That’s right.
[رجل 2] هذا صحيح.
With that knack for drinking bombs
مع تلك الموهبة لشرب القنابل
About Tongju City Would you like me to eat it hot? huh?
نبذة عن مدينة تونغجو هل تريد مني أن آكلها ساخنة؟ هاه؟
[People laughing]
[يضحك الناس]
[Joongho] Drinking alcohol so well How have you been holding on for so long?
[Jongho] شرب الكحول جيدًا كيف كنت تمسك لفترة طويلة؟
I finally I think I found a talent
أنا أخيرا أعتقد أنني وجدت موهبة
[People laughing]
[يضحك الناس]
If you build a culture and arts complex A promise to take care of my share
إذا قمت ببناء مجمع الثقافة والفنون وعد لرعاية حصتي
Don't forget
لا تنسى
Ah, is there any possibility?
آه، هل هناك أي احتمال؟
[laughter]
[ضحك]
But Jay
لكن جاي
[Senior] You were earlier
[كبار] كنت في وقت سابق
Liberty Korea Party lawmakers to reporters Aren't you ignoring me too much?
كوريا الحرية المشرعين الحزب للصحفيين ألا تتجاهلني كثيرًا؟
Politicians can't do that
لا يستطيع السياسيون فعل ذلك
Even if I swear on the inside Pretending to be good on the outside
حتى لو أقسمت من الداخل التظاهر بأنك جيد من الخارج
You have to become an actor half the time.
عليك أن تصبح ممثلاً نصف الوقت.
- Look, our great actors. - [People laughing]
- انظروا، الممثلين العظماء لدينا. - [الناس يضحكون]
[Jay] You have to lay the ground like that.
[جاي] عليك أن تمد الأرض بهذه الطريقة.
I feel like I'm going to crawl out
أشعر وكأنني سأزحف للخارج
[Jungho] Who is crawling out?
[Jungho] من الذي يزحف للخارج؟
I want to fight separately Do you have a partner?
أريد القتال بشكل منفصل هل لديك شريك؟
Chairman
رئيس
Because the chairman is a journalist, Are you close with reporters?
لأن الرئيس صحافي. هل أنت قريب من الصحفيين؟
I am better than Ki Yun-cheol That's the strong one, right?
أنا أفضل من كي يون تشيول هذا هو القوي، أليس كذلك؟
- [People laughing] - Close ties with the media.
- [الناس يضحكون] - علاقات وثيقة مع وسائل الإعلام.
[People laughing]
[يضحك الناس]
Then to the political reporters
ثم إلى المراسلين السياسيين
- Please tell me just one rumor. - [Dark Music]
- من فضلك قل لي شائعة واحدة فقط. - [موسيقى داكنة]
Rumors?
شائعات؟
[Kanghu’s sigh]
[تنهد كانغو]
[Sound of door opening]
[صوت فتح الباب]
[Jay’s tired breathing]
[تنفس جاي المتعب]
[Kanghu] No, what the hell? How much did you drink?
[كانغو] لا، ماذا بحق الجحيم؟ كم شربت؟
Looks like I'm getting drunk too
يبدو أنني أصبحت في حالة سكر أيضًا
I drank a little too much
شربت قليلا أكثر من اللازم
[Jay] There’s nothing we can do.
[جاي] لا يوجد شيء يمكننا القيام به.
[Kanghu] But like this What if I drink too much?
[كانغو] ولكن مثل هذا ماذا لو شربت كثيرا؟
Don't push yourself too hard, hurt yourself
لا تضغط على نفسك كثيرًا، فتؤذي نفسك
- [Sigh] - [Calm music]
- [تنهد] - [موسيقى هادئة]
I'm fine
أنا بخير
I'm worried about the kids
أنا قلقة بشأن الأطفال
Kids?
الاطفال؟
Yes, Hae-mi and Yoo-jeong.
نعم، هاي مي ويو جيونغ.
Still believe in me These are the kids who followed me.
لا تزال تؤمن بي هؤلاء هم الأطفال الذين تبعوني.
Well, I can't tell the truth
حسنا، لا أستطيع أن أقول الحقيقة
You must be in so much trouble.
يجب أن تكون في الكثير من المتاعب.
What do you plan on doing?
ماذا تخطط للقيام به؟
[Sigh] We should meet and talk.
[تنهد] يجب أن نلتقي ونتحدث.
I can't avoid feeling betrayed at all, but
لا أستطيع تجنب الشعور بالخيانة على الإطلاق، ولكن
somehow
بطريقة أو بأخرى
I want to make you hurt less
أريد أن أجعلك تتأذى أقل
[sigh]
[تنهد]
[light laughter]
[ضحكة خفيفة]
[Kanghu] Haejang Ramen? okay?
[كانغو] هايجانج رامين؟ تمام؟
[Jay] Okay
[جاي] حسنًا
[sigh]
[تنهد]
[Jay] Yoojeong-ah, Haemiya
[جاي] يوجيونج آه، هيميا
let's meet up
دعونا نلتقي
[cell phone vibrates]
[يهتز الهاتف الخليوي]
[nervous music]
[موسيقى عصبية]
[Yuna] I’m busy so I’ll reply now
[يونا] أنا مشغول لذا سأرد الآن
Why are you suddenly asking to see me?
لماذا تطلب رؤيتي فجأة؟
Mr. Kanghu
السيد كانغو
[Kanghu] Trust me
[كانغو] ثق بي
no matter what anyone says
بغض النظر عما يقوله أي شخص
I mean
أعني
[light laughter]
[ضحكة خفيفة]
just
فقط
Because thank you
لأن شكرا لك
[light laughter]
[ضحكة خفيفة]
[telephone ringing sound]
[صوت رنين الهاتف]
[Jehyuk] Yes
[جيهيوك] نعم
[Secretary] Chairman, at OCS A reporter came to visit
[سكرتير] رئيس مجلس إدارة OCS جاء أحد المراسلين للزيارة
OCS?
OCS؟
Uh, come on in.
اه، ادخل.
[Sound of putting down the receiver]
[صوت إخماد جهاز الاستقبال]
[Knocking sound]
[صوت طرق]
hello This is OCS reporter Sang-guk Han.
مرحبا هذا هو مراسل OCS سانج جوك هان.
[Awkward laughter]
[ضحكة محرجة]
What happened to you, reporter?
ماذا حدث لك أيها الصحفي؟
- [Jehyuk] Candidate for Tongju mayor? - [Nervous music]
- [جيهيوك] مرشح لمنصب عمدة تونغجو؟ - [موسيقى عصبية]
Me?
أنا؟
[Sang-guk] Ah, ah [laughter]
[سانغ غوك] آه، آه [ضحك]
Oh, you don't know.
أوه، أنت لا تعرف.
This is a political club like ours. It's a rumor going around among reporters.
هذا نادي سياسي مثل نادينا. إنها إشاعة تنتشر بين الصحفيين.
You really have no idea.
ليس لديك أي فكرة حقا.
Huh? Well, from the Liberty Korea Party.
هاه؟ حسنا، من حزب كوريا الحرية.
He is a candidate for this Tongju mayoral election.
وهو مرشح لانتخابات رئاسة بلدية تونغجو.
Appointment of Chairman Song Je-hyuk I heard you are planning
تعيين الرئيس سونغ جي هيوك سمعت أنك تخطط
Why in the Liberty Korea Party?
لماذا في حزب كوريا الحرية؟
I go that way
أذهب بهذه الطريقة
I've never been active at all
لم أكن نشطًا على الإطلاق
As much as Jeonghandang candidate Do Jae-i fresh and
بقدر مرشح Jeonghandang Do Jae-i طازجة و
[Sang-guk] Also, at the orphanage
[سانغ غوك] أيضًا، في دار الأيتام
To young children Well, I heard you were called an angel.
للأطفال الصغار حسنًا، سمعت أنك تدعى ملاكًا.
- [Embarrassed laughter] - If you are an angel
- [ضحكة محرجة] - إذا كنت ملاكاً
Huh? Candidate Do Jae-i, an icon of justice, and It's worth it
هاه؟ المرشح دو جاي آي، رمز العدالة، و إنه يستحق ذلك
This is it
هذا كل شيء
[cell phone vibrates]
[يهتز الهاتف الخليوي]
[Jehyuk] Yes, this is Song Jehyuk.
[جيهيوك] نعم، هذا سونغ جيهيوك.
Jeonghan Ilbo?
جيونغان إلبو؟
[Incoming call sound]
[صوت مكالمة واردة]
[in a low voice] Ah, reporter. Wait a minute
[بصوت منخفض] آه، أيها المراسل. انتظر لحظة
[Sang-guk] Yes, yes
[سانغ غوك] نعم، نعم
yes
نعم
Myeongjin Today?
ميونغجين اليوم؟
- [Soaring music] - [Noisy noise]
- [موسيقى صاخبة] - [ضوضاء صاخبة]
- [Reporters’ questions] - [Camera shutter sound]
- [أسئلة المراسلين] - [صوت مصراع الكاميرا]
[Jay] Now the table is set
[جاي] الآن تم إعداد الطاولة
Can I just herd rabbits?
هل يمكنني فقط تربية الأرانب؟
[Atmospheric music plays]
[تشغيل الموسيقى الجوية]
[Sound of a bottle being set down]
[صوت زجاجة يتم وضعها]
[Jehyuk] In return for making our wedding shine
[جيهيوك] في مقابل جعل زفافنا يلمع
I will serve you once, I will serve you It's late.
سأخدمك مرة واحدة، سأخدمك الوقت متأخر.
Because this is where I live today
لأن هذا هو المكان الذي أعيش فيه اليوم
Eat as much as you want
أكل بقدر ما تريد
It's a very popular topic these days.
إنه موضوع شائع جدًا هذه الأيام.
And then really Aren’t you going to be the mayor of Tongju?
ثم حقا ألن تصبح عمدة تونغجو؟
[Manok’s laughter]
[ضحكة مانوك]
[Gicheol clears his throat]
[غيتشيول يمسح حلقه]
[Yuncheol] Well, not really Because reporters keep pestering me
[يونتشيول] حسنًا، ليس حقًا لأن الصحفيين يواصلون مضايقتي
I shouted that it was unfounded.
صرخت أنه لا أساس له من الصحة.
No, the mayoral candidate Where are the kids playing?
لا، المرشح لرئاسة البلدية أين يلعب الأطفال؟
Where did you get such ridiculous origins?
من أين لك هذه الأصول السخيفة؟
Where are you from?
من أين أنت؟
[Clears cough]
[يزيل السعال]
[Sharp sound effect]
[تأثير صوت حاد]
[Music that heightens tension]
[الموسيقى التي تزيد من التوتر]
[Awkward laughter]
[ضحكة محرجة]
Don't do that, just push me.
لا تفعل ذلك، فقط ادفعني.
[Man-ok] Like Chairman Song A healthy young man
[رجل-حسنا] مثل الرئيس سونغ شاب سليم
Became the mayor of Tongju
أصبح عمدة تونغجو
If I become the congressman's right hand man
إذا أصبحت اليد اليمنى لعضو الكونجرس
I think it would be good for the presidential election as well.
أعتقد أن ذلك سيكون جيدًا للانتخابات الرئاسية أيضًا.
[Yuncheol] Eheh, really, really
[يونتشيول] إيه، حقًا، حقًا
Sprinkling shit on someone else's table Please stop yelling
رش القرف على طاولة شخص آخر من فضلك توقف عن الصراخ
What do you think, Chairman Song?
ما رأيك أيها الرئيس سونغ؟
Thinking?
التفكير؟
Are you interested in politics?
هل أنت مهتم بالسياسة؟
I don't know
لا أعرف
never thought about it Because it doesn't happen
لم أفكر في ذلك قط لأنه لا يحدث
When you make up your mind, tell me
عندما تتخذ قرارك، أخبرني
[Ilgu] Really for the sake of Tongzhou City
[Ilgu] حقًا من أجل مدينة Tongzhou
Willingness to work hard If you stand
الرغبة في العمل الجاد إذا وقفت
[Haemi’s laughter]
[ضحك هيمي]
[Atmospheric music plays]
[تشغيل الموسيقى الجوية]
[Haemi’s speaking voice]
[صوت هيمي الناطق]
[Nervous breathing]
[التنفس العصبي]
Were you here first?
هل كنت هنا أولا؟
[Sound of dishes rattling]
[صوت قعقعة الأطباق]
[sigh]
[تنهد]
[Jay] Now
[جاي] الآن
This is my regular place
هذا هو مكاني المعتاد
Goes well with steak They also do good wine pairing.
سارت الامور بشكل جيد مع شريحة لحم كما أنهم يقومون بإقران النبيذ الجيد.
[Haemi] I’m no good?
[هايمي] أنا لست جيدًا؟
My favorite restaurant that I sometimes trusted is like this.
مطعمي المفضل الذي أثق به أحيانًا هو هكذا.
- I heard you're betraying me. - [Sound of putting down a glass]
- سمعت أنك تخونني. - [صوت وضع كأس]
[Sound of dishes rattling]
[صوت قعقعة الأطباق]
[Clears cough]
[يزيل السعال]
Traveling with Kanghu
السفر مع كانغو
[Yoojeong] Did you like it?
[يوجيونغ] هل اعجبتك؟
[Jay] What about you?
[جاي] ماذا عنك؟
Me what?
انا ماذا؟
Is it okay to get married?
هل من الجيد أن أتزوج؟
[panicked breathing]
[التنفس المذعور]
What's so bad about it?
ما هو السيء في ذلك؟
I had a wish
كان لدي رغبة
Building a perfect family
بناء عائلة مثالية
[Haemi] Oh, that’s right
[هايمي] أوه، هذا صحيح
Jehyuk's article appeared on the Internet today Do you know it's plastered all over the place?
ظهرت مقالة جيهيوك على الإنترنت اليوم هل تعلم أنه مُلصق في كل مكان؟
Liberty Korea Party candidate for Tongju mayor It's rising rapidly
مرشح حزب كوريا الحرية لمنصب عمدة تونغجو انها ترتفع بسرعة
What should I do?
ماذا يجب أن أفعل؟
- [Sound of chopping steak] - If you do something wrong, it's you.
- [صوت تقطيع شريحة لحم] - إذا فعلت شيئًا خاطئًا، فهو أنت.
It looks like you're being pushed out by Jehyuk?
يبدو أن جيهيوك طردك؟
[Yoojeong] Those are all rumors
[Yoojeong] هذه كلها شائعات
Don’t reporters know?
ألا يعلم الصحفيون؟
When it comes to elections Just spreading rumors
عندما يتعلق الأمر بالانتخابات مجرد نشر الشائعات
[Laughing] What's wrong?
[يضحك] ما المشكلة؟
Hey, honestly
مهلا بصراحة
- [Haemi] Jehyuk said rudely. - [Sound of putting down]
- [هايمي] قال جيهيوك بوقاحة. - [صوت الإخماد]
What's missing?
ما هو المفقود؟
Excellent persona, good image
شخصية ممتازة، صورة جيدة
Besides now You are the chairman of the Daeyoungwoon Foundation.
الى جانب الآن أنت رئيس مؤسسة Daeyoungwoon.
Our Mr. Jehyuk
السيد جيهيوك
I said I didn’t want that chairman position either.
قلت إنني لا أريد منصب الرئيس أيضًا.
[Yoojeong] What kind of election is a person like that?
[Yoojeong] أي نوع من الانتخابات هو شخص مثل هذا؟
Even if not
حتى لو لم يكن كذلك
[Jay] Because of that, I have something to say
[جاي] ولهذا السبب، لدي ما أقوله
In Tongju City Decided to build a culture and arts complex
في مدينة تونغجو قررت بناء مجمع للثقافة والفنون
I don't think I can do it with you guys
لا أعتقد أنني أستطيع أن أفعل ذلك معكم يا رفاق
[heavy music]
[موسيقى ثقيلة]
As Haemi said, Mr. Jehyuk.
كما قال هيمي، السيد جيهيوك.
The political world is paying attention now.
العالم السياسي يولي اهتماما الآن.
That kind of person To the foundation where he serves as chairman
هذا النوع من الأشخاص إلى المؤسسة التي يشغل فيها منصب رئيس مجلس الإدارة
Entrusting that big construction project?
تكليف هذا المشروع البناء الكبير؟
It's not dangerous
انها ليست خطيرة
In politics
في السياسة
somehow Because I'm going to try to make someone my own.
بطريقة أو بأخرى لأنني سأحاول أن أجعل شخصًا خاصًا بي.
[Surprise gasp] But how...
[شهقة مفاجئة] لكن كيف...
I told you so
قلت لك ذلك
He betrayed us
لقد خاننا
[Haemi] Was that the condition?
[هايمي] هل كان هذا هو الشرط؟
What are the conditions for joining hands with Yuna?
ما هي شروط التعاون مع يونا؟
Are you throwing us away?
هل تطردنا؟
[Jay] What are you talking about?
[جاي] ما الذي تتحدث عنه؟
Why did I abandon you?
لماذا تخليت عنك؟
[Haemi] That’s enough
[هايمي] هذا يكفي
Now no matter what you say I don't believe it
الآن بغض النظر عما تقوله أنا لا أصدق ذلك
[Yoojeong] Jay
[يوجيونغ] جاي
Just one more time Why not think about it?
مرة أخرى فقط لماذا لا تفكر في ذلك؟
We really need that land
نحن حقا بحاجة إلى تلك الأرض
Wake up, you too!
استيقظ، أنت أيضا!
Jay
جاي
Please Let's think about it again, okay?
من فضلك دعونا نفكر في الأمر مرة أخرى، حسنا؟
- [Haemi] Come out - Please, Jay.
- [هايمي] اخرج - من فضلك، جاي.
- [Haemi] Wake up! - [Yoojeong] Jay
- [هيمي] استيقظ! - [يوجيونغ] جاي
[Haemi] Come out
[هايمي] اخرج
[Yoojeong] Jay!
[يوجيونغ] جاي!
[Yujeong’s surprised exclamation]
[تعجب يوجيونج المفاجئ]
[Haemi] You have become a best friend
[هيمي] لقد أصبحت أفضل صديق
You became a best friend
لقد أصبحت أفضل صديق
Do you go to your favorite restaurant together now?
هل تذهبان إلى مطعمك المفضل معًا الآن؟
But Dojae
لكن دوجاي
There is only one difference between a friend and an enemy.
هناك فرق واحد فقط بين الصديق والعدو.
That we were best friends
أننا كنا أفضل الأصدقاء
That much about you Because I know everything inside out.
هذا الكثير عنك لأنني أعرف كل شيء من الداخل إلى الخارج.
Even your private parts
حتى الأجزاء الخاصة بك
[Calm music plays]
[تشغيل الموسيقى الهادئة]
- [Yuna] Do you regret it? - [Writing sound]
- [يونا] هل أنتِ نادمة على ذلك؟ - [صوت الكتابة]
You kicked them out and stuck with me
لقد طردتهم وعلقت معي
How did you find out about this place?
كيف عرفت عن هذا المكان؟
Because it’s not something to say over the phone I went to the office and
لأنه ليس شيئًا يمكن قوله عبر الهاتف ذهبت إلى المكتب و
The office manager is here
مدير المكتب هنا
What do you mean?
ماذا تقصد؟
[Sound of dishes being set down]
[صوت الأطباق التي يتم وضعها]
[Yuna in the recording] Tell me
[يونا في التسجيل] أخبريني
at ace bar Have you ever seen a suspicious gathering?
في شريط الآس هل سبق لك أن رأيت تجمعا مشبوها؟
[Mingi in the recording] That’s…
[مينجي في التسجيل] هذا...
[nervous music]
[موسيقى عصبية]
[Mingi] About once a month?
[مينجي] مرة واحدة في الشهر تقريبًا؟
General guests are not accepted
لا يتم قبول الضيوف العامين
There are days when the entire store is emptied.
هناك أيام يتم فيها إفراغ المتجر بأكمله.
Once a month?
مرة واحدة في الشهر؟
When is that?
متى يكون ذلك؟
[Yuna] The 18th of every month
[يونا] الثامن عشر من كل شهر
The staff at Ace Bar
الموظفون في Ace Bar
Not even accepting regular guests There's a suspicious meeting going on.
ولا حتى قبول الضيوف العاديين هناك اجتماع مشبوه يجري.
That's it
هذا كل شيء
It was the Angels Club.
لقد كان نادي الملائكة.
Ace Bar is called Angel's Club?
يسمى Ace Bar بنادي الملاك؟
How did you know that?
كيف عرفت ذلك؟
Maybe
ربما
[Jay] Have you met Song Je-hyuk?
[جاي] هل قابلت سونغ جي هيوك؟
This is information I obtained by selling my daughter.
هذه معلومات حصلت عليها من خلال بيع ابنتي.
you
أنت
You have to catch him
عليك أن قبض عليه
[Jay] Thank you
[جاي] شكرا لك
I
أنا
I will definitely find your daughter
سأجد ابنتك بالتأكيد
[Yuna] Did you do something too?
[يونا] هل فعلت شيئًا أيضًا؟
It really made him a star.
لقد جعله نجمًا حقًا.
But
لكن
But would he really run for office?
لكن هل سيترشح فعلا لمنصب الرئاسة؟
I need to make him run for office.
أحتاج إلى جعله يترشح للمنصب.
Even if I grab him by the collar
حتى لو أمسكت به من ذوي الياقات البيضاء
[Jehyuk’s strong breathing]
[تنفس جيهيوك القوي]
[Sound of car door closing]
[صوت إغلاق باب السيارة]
What else do you have to say?
ماذا لديك لتقوله؟
You really
أنت حقا
To Tongju Market Why not run for office?
إلى سوق تونغجو لماذا لا يترشح للمنصب؟
[laughter]
[ضحك]
Earlier, you said something about your background.
في وقت سابق، قلت شيئا عن خلفيتك.
Why did you change your mind?
لماذا غيرت رأيك؟
Chairman Kang Il-gu
الرئيس كانغ إيل غو
I told you to leave Do you know why?
قلت لك أن تغادر هل تعرف لماذا؟
The opponent that his daughter Do Jae-i will defeat
الخصم الذي ستهزمه ابنته دو جاي آي
It's because you're easy
هذا لأنك سهل
[heavy music]
[موسيقى ثقيلة]
- [Yuncheol] So, at this point - [Sigh]
- [يونتشيول] إذن، في هذه المرحلة - [تنهد]
Make sure to step on Dojae.
تأكد من خطوة على Dojae.
Because I will push you
لأنني سوف أضغط عليك
Rep. Ki
النائب كي
Do you want to keep Chairman Kang Il-gu in check? I understand your feelings, but
هل تريد إبقاء الرئيس كانغ إيل غو تحت المراقبة؟ أنا أفهم مشاعرك، ولكن
I want to be used there I have no thoughts?
أريد أن يتم استخدامي هناك ليس لدي أفكار؟
[Yuncheol] One way or another
[يونتشيول] بطريقة أو بأخرى
You have nothing to lose, right?
ليس لديك ما تخسره، أليس كذلك؟
hopefully
نأمل
Tongzhou City is yours.
مدينة تونغتشو لك.
[Sound of car door closing]
[صوت إغلاق باب السيارة]
[cell phone vibrates]
[يهتز الهاتف الخليوي]
[Jay] Let’s meet, Ace, come right away.
[جاي] دعونا نلتقي، آيس، تعال على الفور.
[laughter]
[ضحك]
[Rhythmic music]
[موسيقى إيقاعية]
[President Jeong] Reservations are made today How many teams are there?
[الرئيس جيونج] تم إجراء الحجز اليوم كم عدد الفرق هناك؟
- [Mingi] I guess it’s almost full today, right? - [President Jeong] Oh, really?
- [مينجي] أعتقد أن المكان ممتلئ تقريبًا اليوم، أليس كذلك؟ - [الرئيس جيونج] أوه، حقًا؟
[Mingi] Hello
[مينجي] مرحبا
This is membership only This is where it operates
هذه عضوية فقط هذا هو المكان الذي تعمل فيه
Are you a member?
هل أنت عضو؟
I came to meet a guest.
جئت للقاء ضيف.
My name is Song Je-hyuk.
اسمي سونغ جي هيوك.
We will guide you to the prepared room.
سنرشدك إلى الغرفة المجهزة.
[President Jeong] Come here.
[الرئيس جيونج] تعال هنا.
[Sound of door opening]
[صوت فتح الباب]
[Jehyuk] What’s going on?
[جيهيوك] ماذا يحدث؟
Let's all meet up tonight?
دعونا نجتمع جميعا الليلة؟
Are you busy?
هل أنت مشغول؟
As soon as I sit down, I get to the point.
بمجرد أن أجلس، أصل إلى النقطة.
Pour a glass of that
صب كوبًا من ذلك
[laughter]
[ضحك]
You say you don’t drink alcohol from men?
هل تقول أنك لا تشرب الخمر من الرجال؟
Are you saying you're not a man? to me
هل تقول أنك لست رجلاً؟ لي
[snort]
[شخير]
[Sound of pouring alcohol]
[صوت صب الكحول]
[Sound of putting down a glass]
[صوت وضع الزجاج]
[Jehyuk] One drink Are you trying to reconcile?
[جيهيوك] مشروب واحد هل تحاول المصالحة؟
Or
أو
Did you miss me that day?
هل اشتقت لي في ذلك اليوم؟
[snort]
[شخير]
I made the mistake of thinking that he had asked me to pour him a drink.
لقد أخطأت عندما ظننت أنه طلب مني أن أسكب له مشروبًا.
I feel like I'm going to explode from stress You called me
أشعر وكأنني سأنفجر من التوتر لقد اتصلت بي
[Jay] You must have seen that article.
[جاي] لا بد أنك رأيت هذا المقال.
As if
كما لو
Like you're my rival Talking loudly
وكأنك منافس لي التحدث بصوت عال
[Jay snorts]
[جاي الشخير]
I can't pray
لا أستطيع الصلاة
How are you my rival?
كيف حالك منافسي؟
dare
يجرؤ
From that place
من ذلك المكان
- From, from! - [Nervous music]
- من، من! - [موسيقى عصبية]
[sigh]
[تنهد]
What the hell are people
ماذا بحق الجحيم هم الناس
Why are you questioning my origin like this?
لماذا تشكك في أصلي هكذا؟
[Jehyuk] You do that Aren’t you the granddaughter of the Sundae Guk restaurant?
[جيهيوك] أنت تفعل ذلك ألست حفيدة مطعم Sundae Guk؟
The origin I'm talking about is
الأصل الذي أتحدث عنه هو
Money, background, nothing like that.
المال، الخلفية، لا شيء من هذا القبيل.
Is it an innate quality?
هل هي صفة فطرية؟
[Sound of putting down a glass]
[صوت وضع الزجاج]
Are you curious?
هل أنت فضولي؟
What is Dojae’s dignity?
ما هي كرامة دوجاي؟
Ah, I came here to relieve some stress.
آه، جئت إلى هنا لتخفيف بعض التوتر.
Let's quit
دعونا نتوقف
It's not fun
انها ليست ممتعة
[rustling sound]
[صوت حفيف]
Is this okay?
هل هذا جيد؟
What is this?
ما هذا؟
you were the host
كنت المضيف
[Jay] I heard it was pretty popular
[جاي] سمعت أنها تحظى بشعبية كبيرة
But is it because I’m old now?
لكن هل هذا لأنني كبير في السن الآن؟
You’re not attracted to me at all?
أنت لا تنجذب لي على الإطلاق؟
[secret music]
[الموسيقى السرية]
This is what class means.
هذا هو ما تعنيه الطبقة.
I don't want to give even a single penny Even if he’s a piece of trash
لا أريد أن أعطي حتى فلساً واحداً حتى لو كان قطعة من القمامة
I wish I had called you and made you pour me a drink
أتمنى لو أنني اتصلت بك وجعلتك تصب لي مشروبًا
Tips are courtesy to give
النصائح مجاملة لإعطاء
Did you understand?
هل فهمت؟
[Jehyuk] You
[جيهيوك] أنت
If I become your real rival What are you doing this for?
إذا أصبحت منافسك الحقيقي لماذا تفعل هذا؟
To women in bars like this On the subject of drinking alcohol
للنساء في الحانات مثل هذا فيما يتعلق بموضوع شرب الكحول
[Jay] Becoming the mayor of a city?
[جاي] أن تصبح عمدة المدينة؟
Hey
مهلا
wake up from a dream
استيقظ من الحلم
A place where you can climb
مكان حيث يمكنك الصعود
Yoo-jeong turned his back and climbed up. the chairman's position
أدار يو جيونغ ظهره وصعد. موقف الرئيس
That's it.
هذا كل شيء.
[Jay snorts]
[جاي الشخير]
Well, actually, that space is too much.
حسنًا، في الواقع، هذه المساحة كبيرة جدًا.
you just
أنت فقط
This is the place
هذا هو المكان
bottom
أسفل
[Soaring music]
[موسيقى صاخبة]
[Sound of glass breaking]
[صوت كسر الزجاج]
[Angrily breathing]
[تتنفس بغضب]
[rattling sound]
[صوت قعقعة]
[Rough breathing]
[التنفس الخشن]
[Call connection tone]
[نغمة اتصال المكالمة]
Ah, Rep. Ki.
آه، النائب كي.
This is Song Je-hyuk.
هذا هو سونغ جي هيوك.
[Soft music plays]
[تشغيل الموسيقى الهادئة]
[Yoojeong] The rumor should have ended as a rumor.
[Yoojeong] كان ينبغي أن تنتهي الإشاعة كإشاعة.
Suddenly it's Tongju Market?
فجأة أصبح سوق تونغجو؟
[Jehyuk] Sometimes there are rumors It can also become reality
[جيهيوك] في بعض الأحيان تكون هناك شائعات ويمكن أيضا أن تصبح حقيقة واقعة
But the reality is that bad Isn't it true?
لكن الواقع بهذا السوء أليس هذا صحيحا؟
Our Youngwoon is in crisis right now.
إن Youngwoon الخاص بنا في أزمة الآن.
When I become mayor I can save Youngwoon
عندما أصبح عمدة أستطيع إنقاذ يونغ وون
Guaranteed to happen...
أمر مؤكد أن يحدث...
My opponent is Jae-yi.
خصمي هو جاي يي.
[Yoojeong] How could you I will beat Jay
[يوجيونغ] كيف يمكنك ذلك سوف أتغلب على جاي
[Screaming] Jay, Jay, Jay!
[صراخ] جاي، جاي، جاي!
[dark music]
[الموسيقى المظلمة]
you are still better than me Are you trusting Jay more?
أنت لا تزال أفضل مني هل تثق بجاي أكثر؟
Do I look that funny?
هل أبدو مضحكا إلى هذا الحد؟
[Jehyuk] You were abandoned by Jae-yi, right?
[جيهيوك] لقد تخلى عنك جاي يي، أليس كذلك؟
So, the culture and arts complex It went across the water
إذن مجمع الثقافة والفنون ذهب عبر الماء
Then like this You can't stay still.
ثم مثل هذا لا يمكنك البقاء ساكنا.
We have to stop it somehow!
علينا أن نوقفه بطريقة أو بأخرى!
[sigh]
[تنهد]
your wish
رغبتك
You said it was about creating the perfect family.
لقد قلت أن الأمر يتعلق بتكوين عائلة مثالية.
Then
ثم
help me become mayor
مساعدتي في أن أصبح عمدة
Then Yeongwoondo
ثم يونج ووندو
We can protect our families too
يمكننا حماية عائلاتنا أيضًا
[Nana] I went to another playground
[نانا] ذهبت إلى ملعب آخر
But there I played with a certain lady
ولكن هناك لقد لعبت مع سيدة معينة
My dad knows this woman
والدي يعرف هذه المرأة
That woman is just like her mother You look pretty
تلك المرأة هي تماما مثل والدتها تبدو جميلة
Okay
حسنا
[Yoojeong] I will support your choice
[Yoojeong] سأدعم اختيارك
But
لكن
The only thing that protects Youngun is
الشيء الوحيد الذي يحمي يونغون هو
It's not about creating a perfect family.
لا يتعلق الأمر بتكوين عائلة مثالية.
me
أنا
And I have to protect myself too.
ويجب أن أحمي نفسي أيضًا.
Okay, I will do that.
حسنًا، سأفعل ذلك.
[Yoojeong] Thank you
[يوجيونغ] شكرا لك
me you
لي أنت
I believe it
أنا أصدق ذلك
[Kanghu] Thank you, for meeting me
[كانغو] شكرًا لك على مقابلتي
Why do you want to meet Jay secretly?
لماذا تريد مقابلة جاي سرا؟
[Yuna] Come back with me I'm not asking you to date me
[يونا] عد معي أنا لا أطلب منك مواعدتي
I want to know about the prayer ceremony
أريد أن أعرف عن مراسم الصلاة
Prayer ceremony?
مراسم الصلاة؟
Not even Song Je-hyuk?
ولا حتى سونغ جي هيوك؟
That incident 10 years ago
تلك الحادثة قبل 10 سنوات
It started from a prayer room.
بدأ الأمر من غرفة الصلاة.
[Kanghu] Now Jae-yi Because I'm chasing Song Je-hyuk.
[كانغو] الآن جاي يي لأنني أطارد سونغ جي هيوك.
I don't know if Jay had an incident like that. From that very day
لا أعرف إذا كان جاي قد تعرض لحادث كهذا. منذ ذلك اليوم بالذات
Let's chase after it
دعونا مطاردة بعد ذلك
[laughter]
[ضحك]
It's truly a desperate love
إنه حقاً حب يائس
[Yuna] Mr. Kanghu
[يونا] السيد كانغو
Aren't you being too cruel to me?
ألا تكون قاسيًا جدًا معي؟
[Kanghu] I’m sorry
[كانغو] أنا آسف
But about the prayer ceremony The only person I can ask is you
ولكن عن مراسم الصلاة الشخص الوحيد الذي يمكنني أن أسأله هو أنت
[Interesting music]
[موسيقى مثيرة للاهتمام]
What do you want to know about prayer ceremonies?
ماذا تريد أن تعرف عن مراسم الصلاة؟
I'm threatening Dojae with this.
أنا أهدد دوجاي بهذا.
[Sound of a ledger being closed]
[صوت دفتر الأستاذ وهو مغلق]
Or hand it over to Song Je-hyuk.
أو قم بتسليمها إلى سونغ جي هيوك.
What will benefit me?
ماذا سينفعني؟
[Sound of door opening]
[صوت فتح الباب]
[Haemi] What’s going on?
[هايمي] ماذا يحدث؟
[Jihee] Oh, that’s right, this person
[جيهي] أوه، هذا صحيح، هذا الشخص
[Laughing] He was your groom.
[يضحك] لقد كان عريسك.
I saw you briefly before getting married.
لقد رأيتك لفترة وجيزة قبل الزواج.
- I didn't recognize you. - [Putting down sound]
- لم أتعرف عليك. - [اخماد الصوت]
me
أنا
I saw your groom at the hotel
لقد رأيت عريسك في الفندق
[nervous music]
[موسيقى عصبية]
I heard you were going up to your room?
سمعت أنك ستصعد إلى غرفتك؟
It is also the highest presidential floor.
وهو أيضًا أعلى طابق رئاسي.
- What? - [Jihee’s breath of realization]
- ماذا؟ - [نفس الإدراك لجيهي]
Oh, before your groom gets married. You said you were the host, right?
أوه، قبل أن يتزوج العريس. لقد قلت أنك المضيف، أليس كذلك؟
[Jihee] Still a mutt Aren't you able to stop pooping?
[جيهي] لا يزال المغفل ألا تستطيع التوقف عن التغوط؟
- This is real! - [Jihee’s exclamation of surprise]
- هذا حقيقي! - [تعجب جيهي بالمفاجأة]
Are you going to hit me like this?
هل ستضربني هكذا؟
[Jihee] I’m going
[جيهي] أنا ذاهب
[Sound of door opening]
[صوت فتح الباب]
[Sound of door closing]
[صوت إغلاق الباب]
[sigh]
[تنهد]
[Anxious breathing]
[التنفس القلق]
[Sound of door opening]
[صوت فتح الباب]
[Sound of door slamming shut]
[صوت إغلاق الباب بقوة]
[Yuna] Hey there
[يونا] مرحبًا
Are you Aunt Nana?
هل أنت العمة نانا؟
Ah, yes
اه نعم
Are you here to meet your baby’s mom?
هل أنت هنا لمقابلة والدة طفلك؟
[Light laughter] No.
[ضحكة خفيفة] لا.
fact
حقيقة
I came to see my aunt.
جئت لرؤية عمتي.
Me?
أنا؟
yes
نعم
[Yongpil] What was in it? I don't know, but
[يونغبيل] ماذا كان بداخلها؟ لا أعرف، ولكن
quite a lot was being transported inside
كثيرا جدا تم نقله إلى الداخل
This is Song Je-hyuk’s car.
هذه سيارة سونغ جي هيوك.
Even after business hours I visited again
حتى بعد ساعات العمل لقد زرت مرة أخرى
something from ace bar There seems to be movement
شيء من شريط الآس يبدو أن هناك حركة
In 18 days
في 18 يوما
tomorrow
غدا
What should I do?
ماذا يجب أن أفعل؟
The prayer ceremony [sigh]
مراسم الصلاة [تنهد]
A typical bully
الفتوة النموذجية
[Yuna] Alcohol, drugs
[يونا] الكحول والمخدرات
A typical rich son who likes women?
الابن الغني النموذجي الذي يحب النساء؟
I don't know any more than that
لا أعرف أكثر من ذلك
Even now
حتى الآن
About prayer ceremony Can anyone tell me?
حول مراسم الصلاة يمكن لأحد أن يقول لي؟
Well, a prayer friend or something.
حسنا، صديق الصلاة أو شيء من هذا.
[laughter]
[ضحك]
his friends It's all similar to the prayer ceremony.
أصدقائه كل شيء يشبه مراسم الصلاة.
Mr. Kang-hoo is meeting me. What special story should I tell you?
السيد كانغ هو يقابلني. ما هي القصة الخاصة التي يجب أن أخبرك بها؟
[light sigh]
[تنهد خفيف]
But think a little more
لكن فكر أكثر من ذلك بقليل
[sigh]
[تنهد]
[nervous music]
[موسيقى عصبية]
Yujeong’s orphanage?
دار أيتام Yujeong؟
[Yuna] That guy on the weekend I definitely went there and served.
[يونا] ذلك الرجل في عطلة نهاية الأسبوع بالتأكيد ذهبت إلى هناك وخدمت.
If you don't go
إذا كنت لا تذهب
Ki Yun-cheol is his card. I said I'd cut it off.
كي يون تشيول هي بطاقته. قلت أنني سأقطعها.
[tire rubbing sound]
[صوت احتكاك الإطارات]
[surprised gasp]
[شهقة متفاجئة]
[Kanghu's urgent breathing] Are you okay?
[تنفس كانغو العاجل] هل أنت بخير؟
Blood, ugh, this guy I can't see it
الدم، آه، هذا الرجل لا أستطيع رؤيته
[Kanghu] Ah, blood, blood
[كانغو] آه، الدم، الدم
- [Intense sound effect] - [Student’s terrifying scream]
- [تأثير صوتي مكثف] - [صرخة الطالب المرعبة]
[Soaring music]
[موسيقى صاخبة]
[cell phone vibrates]
[يهتز الهاتف الخليوي]
[Yuna’s surprised gasp]
[شهقة يونا المفاجئة]
[breathing in relief]
[تنفس الراحة]
Now, is everyone ready?
الآن، هل الجميع جاهز؟
[Police] Yes!
[الشرطة] نعم!
[tire rubbing sound]
[صوت احتكاك الإطارات]
[Junghyeon] In our palace district distributing drugs
[Junghyeon] في منطقة قصرنا توزيع المخدرات
There is an illegal secret organization A report has been received
هناك منظمة سرية غير قانونية لقد تم استلام تقرير
- Let’s have fun clearing it out! - [Police] Yes!
- دعونا نستمتع بإزالتها! - [الشرطة] نعم!
[Police talking]
[حديث الشرطة]
[Employee] Hey, wait a minute. Wait, wait, wait
[الموظف] مهلا، انتظر لحظة. انتظر، انتظر، انتظر
[Sound of arguing]
[صوت الجدال]
[Police 1] Drug dealing here There was a report that there was
[الشرطة 1] تجارة المخدرات هنا كان هناك تقرير بأن هناك
Is this real?
هل هذا حقيقي؟
[Police 2] Come out, come out, come out!
[الشرطة 2] اخرج، اخرج، اخرج!
[Police 3] Go straight in.
[الشرطة 3] ادخل مباشرة.
[Sound of people talking noisily]
[صوت الناس يتحدثون بصوت عال]
[Police 4] Miss, give me your handbag and go. Give me the handbag!
[الشرطة 4] يا آنسة، أعطيني حقيبة يدك واذهبي. أعطني حقيبة اليد!
[singing sound]
[صوت الغناء]
[People’s excited exclamation]
[تعجب الناس المتحمس]
[Police 5] Everyone stop moving
[الشرطة 5] توقف الجميع عن الحركة
[Sound of arguing]
[صوت الجدال]
What are you doing now?
ماذا تفعل الآن؟
A person who conducts business with a law-abiding spirit Can I turn you into a druggie like this?
الشخص الذي يمارس الأعمال التجارية بروح الالتزام بالقانون هل يمكنني تحويلك إلى مدمن مخدرات مثل هذا؟
[Call connection tone]
[نغمة اتصال المكالمة]
The lawyer's prediction was correct.
وكان توقع المحامي صحيحا.
There is no Song Je-hyuk here.
لا يوجد سونغ جي هيوك هنا.
[Jai] Tomorrow is the 18th
[جاي] غدا هو الثامن عشر
[Yongpil] What should we do?
[يونغبيل] ماذا يجب أن نفعل؟
[sigh]
[تنهد]
Please prepare first.
يرجى الاستعداد أولا.
[Yongpil] Still a daycare center with angels Are you getting caught?
[يونغبيل] لا يزال مركزًا للرعاية النهارية به ملائكة هل يتم القبض عليك؟
The day of the opening ceremony of the Angels Club
يوم حفل افتتاح نادي الملائكة
Song Je-hyuk is at Cheonrang Orphanage. had a wedding
سونغ جي هيوك موجود في دار أيتام تشونرانج. كان حفل زفاف
the wedding
الزفاف
I thought it was the opening ceremony of the club.
اعتقدت أنه كان حفل افتتاح النادي.
However, in a daycare center with children What can be done?
ومع ذلك، في مركز الرعاية النهارية مع الأطفال ما الذي يمكن عمله؟
- [Sigh] - [Yongpil] As Go Yoo-na said
- [تنهد] - [يونغبيل] كما قالت جو يو نا
ace bar How about hitting it?
شريط الآس ماذا عن ضربها؟
Let's hit two places at once.
دعونا ضرب مكانين في وقت واحد.
[sigh]
[تنهد]
That's right, Chief.
هذا صحيح يا رئيس.
[Jay] It’s not an ace bar This is correct
[جاي] إنها ليست شريطًا رائعًا هذا صحيح
[Junghyun] I only believe in one thing
[Junghyun] أنا أؤمن بشيء واحد فقط
You know that if this goes wrong, it’s over for me, right?
أنت تعلم أنه إذا حدث خطأ ما، فسينتهي الأمر بالنسبة لي، أليس كذلك؟
Yes, let's go
نعم، دعنا نذهب
[Police] Come on, let’s go.
[الشرطة] هيا، لنذهب.
[nervous music]
[موسيقى عصبية]
[Director] No, wait a minute, wait a minute.
[المدير] لا، انتظر لحظة، انتظر دقيقة.
What's going on, this time of night...?
ماذا يحدث في هذا الوقت من الليل...؟
[Jay] Just this It's just the beginning
[جاي] هذا فقط إنها مجرد البداية
I waited 10 years
انتظرت 10 سنوات
The beginning of revenge on you
بداية الانتقام منك
[Embarrassing elasticity]
[مرونة محرجة]
more cruelly
بقسوة أكبر
even more miserable
بل وأكثر بؤسا
I'll trample you down
سوف أدوس عليك
that day
في ذلك اليوم
there
هناك
you showed me
لقد أظهرت لي
In return for that hell
مقابل ذلك الجحيم
[Woman's scream]
[صرخة امرأة]
Now your mask is coming off
الآن سقط قناعك
right away
على الفور
- The moment you open this door - [Sound of door opening]
- في اللحظة التي تفتح فيها هذا الباب - [صوت فتح الباب]
[Sound of door slamming shut]
[صوت إغلاق الباب بقوة]
[Nana] What is it?
[نانا] ما هذا؟
[Yuna] Do you know who this person is?
[يونا] هل تعرف من هو هذا الشخص؟
[Nana] Aunt
[نانا] العمة
Then
ثم
Who is this pretty baby?
من هو هذا الطفل الجميل؟
[Intense sound effect]
[تأثير صوتي مكثف]
[secret music]
[الموسيقى السرية]
[Jehyuk] Choi Kang-hoo?
[جيهيوك] تشوي كانغ هوو؟
[Kanghu] It’s a prayer ceremony.
[كانغو] إنها مراسم صلاة.
Do you remember?
هل تذكر؟
[Jehyuk] Unlucky bastard
[جيهيوك] وغد سيئ الحظ
[Jay] I will soon
[جاي] سأفعل ذلك قريبًا
About the identity of the orphanage I think I can tell
عن هوية دار الأيتام أعتقد أنني أستطيع أن أقول
Then it's the end for Song Je-hyuk.
إذًا إنها نهاية سونغ جي هيوك.
[Jehyuk] Tell me
[جيهيوك] أخبرني
I’m curious too
أنا فضولي أيضًا
Your heart
قلبك
[Yuna] Is it a secret club or something?
[يونا] هل هو نادي سري أم شيء من هذا القبيل؟
First of all, starting with Song Je-hyuk Can't we solve it?
بادئ ذي بدء، بدءًا من سونغ جي هيوك ألا يمكننا حلها؟
- Do you remember the lady? - [Nana] Yes
- هل تتذكر السيدة؟ - [نانا] نعم
[Yuna] I'm looking for Nana One o'clock is urgent
[يونا] أنا أبحث عن نانا الساعة الواحدة أمر عاجل
[Nana’s happy exclamation]
[تعجب نانا السعيد]
[Yoojeong] Because of that past
[Yoojeong] بسبب ذلك الماضي
My precious family now There will be no waking up
عائلتي الكريمة الآن لن يكون هناك استيقاظ
No matter what happens
بغض النظر عما يحدث
I
أنا
I will protect you
سأحميك
[Yoojeong] Promise me one thing
[Yoojeong] أوعدني بشيء واحد
Jay Niga
جاي نيجا
Me and Jehyuk
أنا وجيهيوك
I won't do anything that breaks the family.
لن أفعل أي شيء يكسر العائلة.
I can't do that
لا أستطيع فعل ذلك
[Sigh]
[تنهد]
[Jay] I am your husband
[جاي] أنا زوجك
I can't forgive
لا أستطيع أن أغفر